hey what's up thanks for listening to
the gry Life podcast my name is Jeremiah
Kowski on this podcast we talk about how
coaches mentors and trainers can scale
their businesses to multiple six seven
and even eight figures I've been in this
industry for 22 years and I know what it
takes to get results and that's what I
want to walk you through is how to get
the results that you want in your
business the first step is obviously
knowing who you help and I think if
you're listening to this right now you
know who you want to help you know how
you want to help them but what do you
actually do to launch things well it
takes a series of creating a product
that you're going to sell and then
Gathering a group of people that you can
actually present to and that's one of
the biggest steps that I say that people
need to do is you need to be able to
make presentations and have
conversations with people that will
become potential clients not everybody's
a good fit to become your client when
you can gather the right people in front
of you then you know exactly who to talk
to and you can close sales with them now
what you have to do is you have to
figure out how do I persuade somebody to
be able to take action and become a
client of mine that's the most important
step the only way that we can do that is
by linking it to the desires that
somebody already has so that it becomes
their idea and so if the way that we do
this is that we gather people to listen
to video presentations some kind of
video presentation now we have forms of
content podcasts social media content
YouTube videos you might be watching
those right now this on YouTube those
are preliminary pieces of content or
ways of nurturing trust and building
relationship with people but the what
the ones that we really want to look at
for growing our business have to do with
growing your email list figuring out
what are specific areas of Desire that
your potential clients and when I say
potential clients it's specifically
related to people who are actually going
to spend money with you people who are
actually going to make an investment
with you not everybody is going to make
an investment with you and it's not your
job to try to get people that are not
going to make an investment to change
their mind it's just not possible to do
so you can actually go semi psychosis
and crazy trying to do so so what you
want to do is you want to find the
people that are already pre-qualified
they already have a desire they already
have something that they want to
accomplish a transformation that they're
looking for and they're looking for you
to be able to bring them from where they
are to where they want to be now you got
to have confidence in the fact that you
can deliver that transformation you need
to have a track record of that fact and
maybe you're saying well jerem I don't
have a big track record or a bunch of
case studies or things like that that's
not what I'm talking about you know I
met a lady once she was saying I don't
have anything nothing to prove to people
that I can do this and yet she had built
curriculum for schools for 40 years and
I was like yeah you literally have the
blueprint for coaching people for
educating for all of this but you're
doubting yourself because you haven't
helped somebody make a million dollars
with a course on I'm like ma'am you have
the
skills but you got to translate them in
that way so talk about what you have
experienc in your experiences in your
life might not look exactly like the
million dooll idea or things like that
and and here's the thing is sometimes I
think we get it built up in our head
that I got to have this giant uh result
these giant testimonies for it to be
worth
it go based on what you know how to do
there are people that are out there that
need what you can offer they need the
help that you can offer and they're
looking for somebody to be able to
provide that for them and then you can
find those
people and you give them the thing that
they want you give them the process for
the transformation if you're in a
coaching business that's exactly what we
do we can give them the process we can
help them go through the process of
figuring it out internally for
themselves and one of the best things
that you can do is give away your very
best content
for
free those of you that follow me you
know that that's been my strategy that's
exactly what I do that's why we be a
able to build our business to seven
figures is because I give away my best
content for free everybody say well gosh
if I do that what what are client's
going to pay me for that's the wrong
mindset because the truth is is that if
people are not um in your ecosystem
coaching with you the proximity to you
is what they're paying for the
accountability the support not the
information give the information away
and then help them Implement in your
paid programs when people join my client
growth accelerator I help them actually
apply the stuff that I'm teaching right
now everything that I'm teaching in this
podcast I work with come alongside and
help build and Implement those things
with my clients I'm not able to actually
do that just through a podcast episode
or just through YouTube videos but in
the YouTube videos I give the whole
process away and that's exactly what you
want to do as as a coach and as a
mentors you want to give your processes
away you want to share stories and and
victories and and things that you've
learned along the way things that can
encourage people that they can do it
that they can accomplish it that they
can make it happen for them and then
what you're looking to do is get them to
join your email list now they join the
email list in exchange for some kind of
a private video presentation whether it
be a a a single
recording could be 40 minutes in length
could be 90 minutes in L could be a
3-day intensive that you charge $7 for
like we're hosting on January 15th where
you can actually join us and work with
me and get three days of coaching to be
able to build and launch your business
together and if you're listening after
this time in January 15th we have
upcoming events all the time on my
website ji.com I'd love to have you
become a part of those and to check
those out we have a number of different
trainings as well that we offer people
for free and low cost and that's exactly
what you do is you figure out what can I
offer at at a very low cost or for free
to build trust with people to make a
connection with people to show them to
demonstrate to them that I can
accomplish the thing that I say that I'm
going to do
then the right people who see that you
can help them achieve that goal that you
can help them get from where they are to
where they they want to be they are
going to want to make an investment to
get that ultimate end dream outcome that
they want that that final p pay off that
that
True
Result that they're looking for and so
when we're launching what we have to
look at is we got to create a landing
page we got to write some sales copy we
got to start promoting it to people you
know I made a list for my clients these
four steps a four-part challenge that I
made them for the new year and I'd love
to make this challenge to you as well
the four-part challenge is this is that
to hold yourself accountable this year
turn your sales copy into a landing page
that grows your email list so start
writing sales copy using AI don't take a
lot of time writing it either give
yourself a time limit of like a week or
two to write the sales copy me I give
myself a time limit of an hour or two to
write my sales copy and then I get it
out there but you got to then build it
into a landing page a landing page is
something that people can find on the
internet they can sign up for with their
name and email address from there you
can set up a simple many chat automation
many chat is a tool that allows you to
automate direct messages that come in
from from people through
Instagram and then from there you start
promoting it every day one post a day
for two weeks straight that I on every
platform email marketing social media
and spend a small budget of $10 to $20 a
day promoting with Instagram
ads and by doing this using lowcost
Instagram ads very simple silly reels
when I say silly reels it's literally
like I I I could take a reel of me
sitting at my desk typing pretending
like I'm talking and then I put text
over the reel I run that as an ad and
that gets leads and sales in my business
and so then from there what I what I do
is people join me for
presentations and so the job my job is
to get as many people to register for
that presentation as possible if it's
low cost more people are actually going
to show up for the presentation and
that's what's really cool and that gives
you the ability to actually qualify who
you're going to work with and draw in a
a very qualified group of people that's
willing to make an investment they've
already shown they've been willing to
make an investment because they've made
a small investment with you and they're
willing to move forward to get those
results in their business and so listen
if you're somebody who is trying to
build your business you're trying to get
results it's time for you to create an
offer and launch it out there to people
start promoting it stop letting the fear
and worry dominate you stop letting the
perfectionism stop letting the
insecurity the doubt is this going to
work can I make this work for me
listen there's always a risk it's never
guaranteed but the one thing that is
guaranteed is if you do nothing or you
sit in your hands nothing's going to
work so you got to start to take action
you got to start to move forward instead
of staying stuck and that will be the
first step to you getting
results we have to figure out why are we
staying stuck internally a lot of us
have beliefs and feelings that are
stopping us from doing the things that
we need to do those feelings are often
deceptive they're lying to us and I'm
not gaslighting anybody by saying that
because I've worked with thousands of
people on this is that your feelings
when it comes to launching your business
oftentimes they're very deceptive and
you might say Jeremiah they're they're
so real I don't want to lose money I
don't want to ruin my reputation can I
tell you this you're not going going
to destroy anything by launching your
business might it cost you something and
I I was actually talking to my mentor
today and she said this any business own
that is trying to avoid losing has
already
lost and so realize that part of the
process
is figuring out okay there is a risk I
got to take action I'm never going to
have it all perfect and put together
it's time for me to start to move
forward in the position that I'm at
right
now it's not guaranteed that you're
going to make six or seven figures when
you start building your
business there's no way to guarantee
that but what is guaranteed is if you
stay consistent you will start start to
see results if you stay plugged in if
you start if you work with somebody like
myself to be able to build your business
if you work with me specifically I can
definitely tell you we'll help you get
results all right stay plugged into this
podcast join us for one of our Live
Events and jump into my accelerator
program we'll talk soon have a good one
[Music]
[Applause]